buyology.com.ng 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy**

 Welcome to Buyology’s privacy policy. We ensure the protection and proper use of your personal information and are committed to protecting your personal information in our possession. In order to preserve your trust, we want you to understand what personal information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of this information.

In this policy, "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name (first and last), address (city, state,), e-mail address, telephone number, etc.

This Privacy Policy governs your experience on our website unless otherwise indicated.

**Information We Collect**

We collect personal information when communicating or interacting with you through our website. Some examples include:  
•    Registering for a shopping account or Wish list.  
•    When you request that items be sent to you or others, make purchases or returns with us, place an order with us online, via phone, e-mail.  
•    Fulfilling orders you place and delivering them.  
•    Communications from us or when offering recommendations to you  
•    Your Financial Account details when transacting with us  
•    Interacting with our websites or mobile sites, mobile applications and services  
•    Working with us to assist with your needs and purchases  
•    Contacting us with a comment, question or complaint  
We may combine all information we collect and we may disclose this information within our service providers. When you visit our website we may also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or other device identifiers, browser information, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, location, date/time stamp and clickstream data.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use the personal information that we collect to conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products, services and experience. We may collect and use your information to provide you products and services, to respond to your comments, questions or complaints, determine your satisfaction with our programs and service, to personalize your experiences, if you ask us to, send you marketing communications and other information you have chosen to receive regarding our products, services, marketing or special events. We also use your personal information for our everyday business purposes such as payment processing, analytics, fraud prevention, reporting, making back-ups and legal compliance.

**How We Share Your Information**

To best serve you, we may share your personal information with  service providers that provide support services to us or that help us market our products and services, administer our programs, operations and fulfill your request. Service providers, third parties who perform services on our behalf, are contractually restricted from using your information in any manner other than in helping us to provide you with the products and services available from Buyology. We may also, in certain instances, disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, detect and protect you or us from fraud, manage information security or bring legal action to protect your rights or the rights of Buyology or others. We may also disclose your personal information when you ask us to do so or when we believe it is required or permitted by law

.  
**Cookies and Other Similar Technologies**

Our website uses "cookie” technology. A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to identify your device, provide website user authentication, conduct fraud prevention and management services, distinguish you from other visitors, record your IP address and understand your use of our site, and identify the name of the Web site from which you linked to Buyology. This information is used for fulfilling contracts with our business partners, and to help us serve you better by improving our website design, as well as our products, services, and promotions. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites. Information obtained through cookies may be shared with or obtained by service providers on our behalf.

**Social Media Interaction     **  
Facebook invites you to socialize and share your fa inspiration, finds and purchases with your friends using Social Media tools such as Facebook and Twitter. If you choose to use these tools, you may be sharing certain profile elements, including your comments. This sharing is subject to each social media program's privacy policies.

**Security   **

  We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of personal information transmitted to us using this website. To help guard your information, our website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your card number, name and address so only Buyology is able to decode your information. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.
